<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blockchain on Cryptuon</title><link>/tags/blockchain/</link><description>Recent content in Blockchain on Cryptuon</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>© Cryptuon 2020-23</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/blockchain/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About us</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>Founded by the team behind Boom Labs, Cryptuon is at the forefront of next-generation blockchain technologies and services. Despite Boom Labs&amp;rsquo; shutdown, the innovative strides, including the development of a multi-chain API, an MPC wallet, and a high-scale cloud infrastructure, continue to fuel Cryptuon&amp;rsquo;s innovative journey. With a firm belief in blockchain technology&amp;rsquo;s potential, we are pioneering groundbreaking projects, backed by confidence from investors and publicly listed companies.</description></item><item><title>Contact us</title><link>/contact/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/contact/</guid><description>Cryptuon invites you to connect with us for any queries, advice, or interests in our blockchain technologies and services. Our team is ready to answer your questions, discuss your blockchain needs, and offer expert advice. If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a career in blockchain, we&amp;rsquo;re eager to explore opportunities with you. Whatever your reason for reaching out, let&amp;rsquo;s start your blockchain journey with Cryptuon.</description></item><item><title>Design Intern at Cryptuon 🎨🚀</title><link>/jobs/design-intern-at-cryptuon/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/jobs/design-intern-at-cryptuon/</guid><description>Cryptuon, a pioneer in blockchain technologies and Web3 services, is on the lookout for a creative and dedicated Design Intern to join our team.</description></item><item><title>Frontend Developer Intern at Cryptuon 💻🚀</title><link>/jobs/frontend-developer-intern-at-cryptuon/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/jobs/frontend-developer-intern-at-cryptuon/</guid><description>At Cryptuon, we&amp;rsquo;re driving innovation in blockchain technologies and Web3 services, and we&amp;rsquo;re looking for a talented and enthusiastic Frontend Developer Intern to join our team.</description></item><item><title>Marketing Intern at Cryptuon 🚀💼</title><link>/jobs/marketing-intern-at-cryptuon/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/jobs/marketing-intern-at-cryptuon/</guid><description>Cryptuon, a trailblazer in the world of blockchain technologies and Web3 services, is looking for a motivated and dynamic Marketing Intern with a focus on growth and social media.</description></item><item><title>Smart Contract Development Intern at Cryptuon 🚀🔒</title><link>/jobs/smart-contract-development-intern-at-cryptuon/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/jobs/smart-contract-development-intern-at-cryptuon/</guid><description>Cryptuon, a leading innovator in blockchain technologies and Web3 services, is seeking a passionate and proactive Smart Contract Development Intern.</description></item><item><title>Cryptuon</title><link>/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/</guid><description>Cryptuon leverages the disruptive power of blockchain and Web3 to revolutionize digital landscapes. We are at the forefront of this technology, offering state-of-the-art solutions and protocols for businesses of all sizes. Our goal is to provide a more transparent, secure, and efficient digital future. As your partner, we provide expert advice and assistance, making us a one-stop-shop for all your blockchain needs.</description></item><item><title>Jobs</title><link>/jobs/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/jobs/</guid><description>Cryptuon is keen to recruit talented individuals passionate about blockchain and Web3 technologies. If you&amp;rsquo;re ready to immerse yourself in this transformative field, explore our open positions and see how you can contribute to the blockchain revolution. With Cryptuon, you can make a real impact.</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>/projects/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/projects/</guid><description>At Cryptuon, we&amp;rsquo;re actively building the future of blockchain and Web3 technologies. Our innovative projects range from pioneering new protocols to integrating blockchain with automation and empowering businesses with cutting-edge AI tools. Alongside our expert consulting services, we are making significant strides in revolutionizing the blockchain space. Learn more about our exciting endeavors.</description></item><item><title>Writings</title><link>/writings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/writings/</guid><description>Our team of experts presents comprehensive and insightful articles on blockchain and Web3, offering readers an in-depth understanding of the latest trends and technologies. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a novice or a seasoned professional in the blockchain realm, our written works are a treasure trove of valuable insights to enhance your knowledge. Stay ahead of the curve by immersing yourself in our educational content.</description></item></channel></rss>