<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blockchain Projects on Cryptuon</title><link>https://www.cryptuon.com/tags/blockchain-projects/</link><description>Recent content in Blockchain Projects on Cryptuon</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>© Cryptuon 2020-23</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.cryptuon.com/tags/blockchain-projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About us</title><link>https://www.cryptuon.com/about/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.cryptuon.com/about/</guid><description>Founded by the team behind Boom Labs, Cryptuon is at the forefront of next-generation blockchain technologies and services. Despite Boom Labs&amp;rsquo; shutdown, the innovative strides, including the development of a multi-chain API, an MPC wallet, and a high-scale cloud infrastructure, continue to fuel Cryptuon&amp;rsquo;s innovative journey. With a firm belief in blockchain technology&amp;rsquo;s potential, we are pioneering groundbreaking projects, backed by confidence from investors and publicly listed companies.</description></item><item><title>Design Intern at Cryptuon 🎨🚀</title><link>https://www.cryptuon.com/jobs/design-intern-at-cryptuon/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.cryptuon.com/jobs/design-intern-at-cryptuon/</guid><description>Cryptuon, a pioneer in blockchain technologies and Web3 services, is on the lookout for a creative and dedicated Design Intern to join our team.</description></item><item><title>Frontend Developer Intern at Cryptuon 💻🚀</title><link>https://www.cryptuon.com/jobs/frontend-developer-intern-at-cryptuon/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.cryptuon.com/jobs/frontend-developer-intern-at-cryptuon/</guid><description>At Cryptuon, we&amp;rsquo;re driving innovation in blockchain technologies and Web3 services, and we&amp;rsquo;re looking for a talented and enthusiastic Frontend Developer Intern to join our team.</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://www.cryptuon.com/projects/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.cryptuon.com/projects/</guid><description>At Cryptuon, we&amp;rsquo;re actively building the future of blockchain and Web3 technologies. Our innovative projects range from pioneering new protocols to integrating blockchain with automation and empowering businesses with cutting-edge AI tools. Alongside our expert consulting services, we are making significant strides in revolutionizing the blockchain space. Learn more about our exciting endeavors.</description></item></channel></rss>